Sanghoon (Austin) Jung

1247 Lakeside DR. Apt. 2022, Sunnyvale, CA 94085 (650) 335-8730 austinjung@live.ca

LinkedIn

Page 1

Profile

More than 10 years' experience of software programming

- Full experience of large-scale software systems development and implementation
- Strong responsible, diligent and understanding personality
- Excellent problem solver and team player with good communication skills and open mind
- Ability to work independently in order to meet deadlines with detail oriented
- Excellent customer care and support experience
- Enjoy challenges, hardworking and accomplishment
- Enjoy learning new computer & software technologies

Technical Skills

Programming languages Python, C#.NET, VB.NET, Java, PHP, and C/C++

Operating systems Windows and Linux

Web programming Django, UI Bootstrap, AngularJS, React, jQuery, Javascript,

HTML5, Silverlight, ASP.NET,

Messaging and Task RabbitMQ, Celery, Redis

Database MS-SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL and MongoDB

Software Tools Pycharm , Microsoft Visual Studio, Eclipse

DVC/SCM Git, Bitbucket, Stash,

Agile Project Management Two weeks scrum using Jira

Continuous integration Jenkins, CircleCl and Docker

Education _____

BCIT (British Columbia Institute of Technology) Jan. 2010 ~ Dec. 2010 Burnaby, BC, Canada

- The Applied Software Development Program Associate Certificate
 - System Analysis and Design
 - Software Development
 - Java Application Development
 - .NET Windows Application Development

Han Yang University

Mar. 1980 ~ Feb. 1984

Seoul, Korea

Bachelor's degree of Electronic Communication Engineering

Professional Experience

Software Engineer

July, 2017 ~ Current

Carta, San Francisco, CA

- Develop Investor Service Web Application. Python/Django/React
 - Capital call management with escrow bank account
 - Reconcile LP transfer money to Fund
 - Decouple Fund commitment from Certificate

Software Engineer

Aug, 2015 ~ Apr, 2017

CopperTree Analytics, Surrey, BC, Canada

- Enhance Kaizen/Estimator for internal sales team and partners. -- Python
- Integrate Kaizen/Estimator with Microsoft Dynamic GP for invoicing
- Suggest change framework from web2py/pysander to Python/Django Rest Framework
- Suggest TDD methodology for new API project
- Manage & lead the new API project.
 - Replace Alembic with django ORM.
 - Provide API endpoints for partners using Python.
 - Restructure API endpoints for internal application using Python.

Software Engineer

July, 2013 ~ Aug, 2015

Kerkhoff Technologies, Chilliwack, BC, Canada

- Developed Web applications for Multapplied Networks Inc. using Python/Django, Django Rest Framework and AngularJS with UI Bootstrap.
- Agile development with continuous integration environment using Jira, Git, and Jenkins.
- Developed Connusion using Python/Django Connectwise to Infusionsoft Integration.
- Deployed Connusion on Apache Tomcat cloud server.

Web Programmer/Developer

Feb, 2011 ~ Jun, 2013

Columbia Kitchen Cabinets Limited, Abbotsford, BC, Canada

- Developed an online configurator for our dealers to manage their orders and quotations.
 - https://nq.columbiacabinets.com
- Developed inventory management systems for touch screen PCs and tablet PCs.
 - C#.NET in WPF and ASP.NET for Restful APIs with JQuery Mobile

IT(Information Technology) Consultant/Developer

Jan, 1999 – Dec, 2002

i2 Technologies Korea Branch, Seoul Korea

- Diagnosed the customer's business problems & needs and sought solutions for the customer.
- Delivered software solutions and technical services to the customer in support of the overall solution.